Hello friends, welcome to today's
video. In today's video, we will talk
about some stocks
which are being seen in the TT market today on the basis of news.
First of all, we will talk about Bank Nifty and Nifty. There is a lot of
pressure being seen in both of them. They are
seen trading at lower levels today. So
let's move towards our first stock.
Talking about the first stock, here
Son Energy is basically what is So Energy, the company
approved raising 000 crores in multiple
instruments. Here, Rs. 4000 crores were
seen being raised
from different instruments like
debenture bonds, which are the instruments available in the market here.
Rs. 4000 crores can be seen being raised here.
Son Energy can be found here. So, if we
talk about now, it is trading in the online market around 5175 paise. It is
almost
down, you can consider it flat. Let's
move towards the next stock. So,
talking about the next stock, here is
PNB.  The bank approved raising
Rs 7500 crore in one or more transactions during the next financial year. In the
next
financial year, Rs 7500 crore can be
seen being raised
here through FP and QIP.
PNB can be seen raising here. If we
talk about now, the flat here is
also trading at 5555 paise. It is
seen trading in today's trading session.
Let us talk about the next talk.
Some interesting news is coming out in this ICICI Bank.
The company received a
demand of Rs 1728 crore. Here,
GST notice is being seen. From
when to when is the penalty on this crore?
From July 2017 to March 2022,
so GST notice of Rs 78 crore is being seen.
Penalty is being seen separately in this.
Basically, the company has
also commented on this and the company has directly
refused to pay it here. They are saying that it will
go to the court there.  But whatever the
file is, it will appeal to the court, so it remains to be
seen what will happen. If we
talk about the present, it is trading below ₹ here, it is seen
doing counter trading,
so let
us talk about the next stock, Aditya
Bala Fashion and Retail, basically the company
raises its stake unit, Finish International, in this, the
stake increase has been seen here,
earlier the stake was at 587, the
stake was seen at 63.5 here,
with what cost, after investing 20 crore rupees, the
stake increase has been seen here,
a beef real, if we talk about it, the
above here is seen in today's trading session, it is doing
counter trading around 24, so let's talk about
Innos's
big share here, the company will
invest 25 crores in Jayam Digital, its own
subsidiary here, it will be seen investing 25 crores here,
approximately if we talk about the counter, then
0.5
At 0.15, it is trading 7 down. It is
seen trading around the price of 5141. You can consider it almost flat. There is
no major decline seen here. However, the news has
come out positive here. So, if we
talk about next year, then Cama Holdings,
basically in Cama Holding, the
promoter was seen selling 17234 shares,
which is at 0.05.
Basically, here, to sell at 75, one can see the selling here.
This is
basically the rule of Savvy. No
promoter can keep his holding above 75 here.
Whenever an
IPO comes, you will have to keep it at 75 within 3 years.
Maintenance is compulsory at 75. Below 76, you will have to keep the promoter holding, so
let us now move towards the next stock here. So,
OMC Oil Marketing,
basically, according to the report, there is
news here that the
prices of petrol and diesel are now going to come down.
You will get it, as it has been said from before that
you will see the prices of petrol and diesel
decreasing, similarly
here the discussion is going on now, so this was some
news which I have tried to tell,
if you liked the video then
like the video and subscribe to the channel
and below I have given the link to open a demat account, if you
want you
can also open your demat account from there, thank you
for watching this video.